Guide to the Miriam Jaffe Papers Documenting Lesbian and Gay Student Life at Yale
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Miriam Jaffe papers documenting lesbian and gay student life at Yale
1979-1992
MS 1945
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.75
(2 boxes)
The papers document Miriam Jaffe's participation in lesbian and gay student life at Yale and in New Haven, as well as her party production company, MJ Productions. The papers consist of advertisements, event calendars, programs, newsletters and playbills.
Jaffe, Miriam
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Miriam Jaffe, 2009.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
Miriam Jaffe graduated from Yale College in 1982. She was active in feminist and gay and lesbian organizations at Yale, including the YaLesbians and the Gay Student Center, and in New Haven's lesbian and gay community. Jaffe produced parties under the name MJ Productions that were popular among gay men and lesbians on campus.
Scope and Contents
The papers document Miriam Jaffe's participation in gay and lesbian student life at Yale and in New Haven, as well as her party production company, MJ Productions. The papers consist of advertisements, event calendars, programs, newsletters and playbills.
Arrangement
The records are arranged alphabetically by organization name.
College students; Gay men -- Connecticut -- New Haven; Lesbians -- Connecticut -- New Haven; LGBTQ resource; Jaffe, Miriam; Yale University -- Students
- Yale related
  - Alliance Bi-weekly, newsletter, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Feminist Film Society, season passes, circa 1980s (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gay and Lesbian Alumni, newsletter, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Gay Student's Center, event calendar, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Days, event calendar, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - MJ Productions, posters, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Pierson College Cabaret, posters, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate Women's Caucus, playbill, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Women's Center, newsletter, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - YaLesbians, flyer, circa 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Non-Yale
  - Memorials of friends, 1984-1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - New Haven organizations and activities, circa 1980s (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Scope and Contents
    Consists of posters, newsletters, publications, especially relevant for AIDS Project New Haven.
  - New York, miscellaneous periodicals, circa 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)